

Resume

Personal details

David Stiven Silva Velandia

davidsilvav6@gmail.com

(321) 310 1615

CARRERA 18 R # 63 F - 14
SUR

Skills

Microsoft Office •••• •••• **Teamwork Customer Service** •••• **HTML Programming JavaScript** •••• Leadership **Web Development Python Programming** Language

Languages

Spanish

English

French

German

Profile

Almost 3 years of experience in the BPO industry and 4 years of experience in customer service. Committed to working hard, keeping discipline, consistency, and teamwork to achieve goals and success.

Currently, studying programming to combine both customer service and technological skills. I have developed my soft skills to handle difficult situations in the best way to find quick and accurate resolutions.

Education

Jan 2023 - Present Software Engineering

FUNDACIÓN UNIVERSITARIA COMPENSAR,

Bogotá

Jan 2023 - Present Full Stack Programming

CODERHOUSE, Bogotá

Jan 2017 - Dec 2022 Modern Languages

UNIVERSIDAD ECCI, Bogotá

Employment

May 2022 - Present

PREMIUM TECHNICAL SUPPORT & SALES REPRESENTATIVE

ASURION, Bogotá

As a Technical Support Agent at Asurion since 2022, I have been at the forefront of providing comprehensive technical assistance to customers, specializing in phones, tablets, computers, and televisions. My role involves adeptly troubleshooting and resolving a spectrum of technical issues, ranging from software glitches to hardware malfunctions. Additionally, I have honed my communication skills to effectively convey complex technical information in a clear and concise manner.

Feb 2021 - Feb 2022

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE

TELEPERFORMANCE, Bogotá

I played a main role in a campaign where I honed my technical skills and customer service approach. My responsibilities extended to finding resolutions by using the resources on hand. Additionally, I consistently demonstrated proficiency in handling escalated technical concerns, collaborating closely with different teams to ensure timely problem resolution. I have experience with multichannel communication, such as phone calls, emails, and real-time chats with customers.

Jan 2020 - Dec 2020

SELLER - INVOICE CLERK - BLOG WRITER

TUBICI BIKE SHOP, Bogotá

I contributed to "Tu Bici Bike Shop", a prominent retailer specializing in bicycles and accessories. In my technical role, I demonstrated a nuanced understanding of the cycling industry and its corresponding technologies. I provided support to guide customers through both the pre-sales and post-sales processes.